

# **Krunal Shah**

Sr .Net Developer

**Phone**: 9429213300

Address: C/6, Green Villa Appt, Nr. HB Kapadiya School

Gurukul Road, Memnagar, Ahmedabad-380052

**Email:** shahkrunal258@gmail.com



Over 8 years of experience in web development such as developing dynamic applications with top technologies. Deep knowledge of .NET Core, Asp.NET MVC, Web Forms, Sql Server, Oracle, Azure, HTML5, Javascript and CSS3, etc. and a Microsoft Certified:

Azure Developer Associate and also worked on Node JS Also had experience on a team handling.

My professional development is not limited to work experience. I constantly improve my technical skills and practical knowledge through working on projects and reading articles.

My long term goal is want to see myself at a respectable position in the company where my decision hold some importance and subordinators look up to me for the inspiration.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Clarion Technologies**

Feb 2022 - Present

### Sr. Software Engineer

- Najm Insurance WhatsApp backend API
- Najm Insurance IVR System API
- Worked on Saudi Arabia based client with backend projects

Company Website: https://www.clariontech.com/

## **Prompt Softech pvt Ltd**

*May 2020 - Feb 2022* 

### Sr. Software Engineer

- TVS Motors Website & Backend API for Mobile
- US based POB Company that prove HR related service and we have created Custom client specific product
- Worked on US based Investment organization and Nop commerce related development

Company Website: https://www.promptsoftech.com/

# Varologic Technologies Private Limited

July 2019 - March 2020

## Software Engineer

Victorian Plumbing Uk's Leading E commerce Website and Warehouse management system

- Victorian Plumbing Uk's Leading E commerce Website in Asp.Net MVC C# With SQL Server 2016 Database
- Warehouse management system Windows Based Software for inventory in shop and Reports & API Project for Mobile application
- Multiple Payment method's and refund module, shipping module with third party API integration & Windows service for Sync Data between two Database
- Worked in Asp.net Core API For IVR Callstream Payment Method
- https://www.victorianplumbing.co.uk/

Company Website: http://www.varologic.com/

### **TM SYSTEMS**

November 2017 — July 2019

### Software Engineer

Auto Bank Core Banking Software

- Core Banking Software in Asp.Net C# With Oracle 11g Database
- Online Banking With security & Rich crystal reports Development
- Console Application for transaction & Working with Rest api
- Mobile application web services and api integration

Company Website: https://www.tmspl.com/

# **INFLIBNET**, Gandhinagar

October 2015 - November 2017

Project Associate (CS)

UGC Website (INFLIBNET):

- Developing University Grant Commission (UGC) Website.
- Developing various Schemes in e-Scholarship-Fellowship Award Registration Tracking System(e-SART)
- Maintaining Existing UGC Website and Database of Website and e-SART.
- Other Project : NIRF(National Institutional Ranking Framework)

Company Website: https://www.inflibnet.ac.in

## White Pearl It Solution Pvt.Ltd.

June 2014 — October 2015

Jr. Programmer (.NET Technology)

Dynamic Website and E commerce Website Development:

- Booksforyou :Ecommere Dynamic Website, Asp.net C# 4.0, MS Sql Server, Payment Gateway
- albatra.com: Ecommere Dynamic Website, Asp.net C# 4.0, MS Sql Server, Payment Gateway, Stock maintain from multiple location throw web services
- Royalcircuits: Online circuit order system and dynamic website, Asp.net C# 4.0, MS Sql Server, Payment Gateway
- Growmore Insurance: An Application to maintain insurance data with reminder sms, email with dynamic reports, Dynamic website
- Other Project : epfahmedabad, Rajkot supermarket etc.

Company Website: http://www.whitepearl.biz/

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Ganpat University**

April 2012 - March 2014

MSc(IT)

Obtained the MSc(IT) degree with 7.0 OUT OF 10 CGPA (64.89 %)

# **Ganpat University**

April 2009 — March 2012

BSc(CA&IT)

Obtained the BSc(CA&IT) degree with 5.47 OUT OF 9.0 CPI (65%)

# Gujarat Secondary and Higher Secondary Education Board

March 2009

12th (HSC)

Obtained the 12th HSC degree with 74.43%

# **Gujarat Secondary and Higher Secondary Education Board**

March 2007

10th (SSC)

Obtained the 10th SSC degree with 67.23%

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Excellent knowledge of C#, VB and creating dynamic Applications in .Net Core, ASP.Net MVC, .Net Framework 4.5 , web forms, ASP.Net MVC API , ASP.Net Core API
- Excellent knowledge of Structured query language (SQL). Working with SQL Server 2008 to 2016, sql maintenance plan, clustered and nonclustered indexes in sql, triggers, cursor, Normalization, sp,Functions, jobs
- Excellent knowledge of Oracle Database 10g and 11g. Oracle Procedure, Functions, trigger, indexes, dump file for backup, normalization
- Excellent knowledge on working with Azure services like App service and VM, Cosmos DB, blob storage, service bus, Azure AD, Azure Functions, Notification hub, etc.
- Knowledge of working with Node JS & Angular JS and Angular CLI 9.
- Knowledge of creating and integration of Web Api and Web services and integration
- Knowledge of working with ADO.NET, Entity Framework 6.0, Ling and Dapper ORM
- Knowledge of working with Source controls like Microsoft Visual SourceSafe (VSS), git, SVN, and Microsoft TFS with Branching, Merging, Automating Build, Test, And Deployment For .NET Projects and git repository management

- Knowledge of working with SAP Crystal Reports 14 with sub reports
- Knowledge of Payment Gateway Module Integration (PayPal, CCavenue, authorize .net, stripe, IVR Call Stream, Berkeley payment) and external login like Facebook, Google Plus etc. and other tools for eCommerce
- Knowledge of hosting website in Internet Information Server (IIS) web server, SSL Integration
- Knowledge of Website security integration like blind sql injection, Session Fixation, Unrestricted File Upload(Non Executable)
- Knowledge of working with custom controls and External controls like AJAX Controls, telerik control etc.
- Knowledge of SMS Integration and Bulk Email Send.
- Expert knowledge of HTML (4, 5), CSS (2,3), bootstrap, material design etc.
- JavaScript, ¡Query skills implement ¡Query pluqins (carousels, sliders, Datatable, JQqrid etc.)
- Strong error handling Skill using External tools NLOG, Rapid7 for Error Log Management and Analyses
- Skills in optimizing websites for mobile display responsive, Export to PDF, URL rewriting
- Knowledge of open source cms like Nopcommerce (.NET), Mr CMS (.NET), wordpress(PHP),joomla(PHP)
- Knowledge of social media marketing, SEO, Google Analytics, Google My Business, Google Map
- Knowledge of Lucene.net integration with faceted search and also basic knowledge of NO SQL (Mongo DB)
- Knowledge of Structured data format like Json and XML

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth: Feb 7th, 1992

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Married

Parent's Name: Mr. Gopalbhai M. Shah

### Languages Known

- English Read, Write, Speak
- Hindi Read, Write, Speak
- Gujarati (Mother tongue) Read, Write, Speak

## Strengths

- Smart working rather than hard working
- I am always try to learn that person who do better than me in any field
- Fighting against odd

### **Interests**

- Travelling
- watching videos in You tube
- Games on PC

### **Extra Activities**

- First winner of Code Ninja Event Held at Prompt Softech
- I have participated in Android and Network Programming Workshop held on DCS Campus, Ganpat University.
- I have participated in Microsoft india AppFest 2013 held on Ganpat University.
- I have participated in Oracle Database 10g: Administration Workshop.
- I have participated in Workshop in java and Code Warzz held by AMPICS, Ganpat University.

### REFERENCES

# Shri Ashok Kumar Rai

Scientist-D(CS)

INFLIBNET Centre,Infocity Gandhinagar, Gujarat Email: ashok@inflibnet.ac.in Phone: 079 2326 8240

#### **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that the above mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge And I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above mentioned particulars.

# **KRUNAL SHAH**